(Penny:)Hey, how are things going
with your parents?
Not great.
They hired divorce attorneys.
(Sheldon:)You know, speaking
of attorneys,
(Sheldon:)if I ever needed
a lawyer,
(Sheldon:)I would not hire
She-Hulk.
(Penny:)You know what?
That was almost on topic.
(Penny:)I'm gonna say,
"Good job, Sheldon."
(Amy:)Wait, She-Hulk's
a lawyer?
(Howard:)Yeah, she works at
a law firm in New York.
(Sheldon:)Yes, but she's the only
monster at the firm.
(Sheldon:)Between you, me
and the wall,
(Sheldon:)I think she's an
affirmative action hire.
(Raj:)Anyway, Dad's gonna
be here in town,
(Raj:)so I won't be able to do
Christmas dinner this year.
(Amy:)If you're not up
to hosting Christmas dinner,
(Amy:)I'm happy to do it.
(Amy:)You can even
bring your father.
(Raj:)That would be nice.
(Amy:)I've always wanted to do
(Amy:)a traditional
Victorian Christmas.
Parlor games,
goose and figgy pudding...
Ugh!
(Sheldon:)English pudding.
Y-You get yourself all
excited for pudding,
(Sheldon:)and here comes a cake
with raisins in it.
(Sheldon:)I'm not going.
(Amy:)You're going.
(Sheldon:)Why do you hate me?
(Amy:)I don't hate you.
(Amy:)I love you.
(Sheldon:)Well, you call it love,
(Sheldon:)but it has a lot
of raisins in it.
(Raj:)Amy, good luck getting
these guys excited
(Raj:)about a dinner
with a theme.
(Raj:)I gave up when no one cared
about my Tom Hanks-giving.
(Bernadette:)I think a Victorian Christmas
sounds nice.
(Howard:)I agree.
Why not?
(Penny:)Me, too.
You guys suck!
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪